Nevil Godar discovered the keys to the
manifestation and achievement of our
desires his life was completely
dedicated to teaching about the
immense power that we possess as
human beings as individuals who are part
of a creative universe Neville guided us
in understanding how to access and take
advantage of this creative facet that
resides in each one of
us order ego wait you can
order the universe what you want and the
easiest and most effective way to
manifest what you want is to know
exactly what it is that you want for
it before going to sleep close your eyes and
communicate with yourself with your heart
knowing that the self of man is God
you are capable of manifesting what you
truly desire trust do not communicate
with others communicate with yourself with your
inner being put aside the thoughts and
focus on the feelings your mind is
the character that you learned to be in
this world put it aside you do not need to
fulfill the dreams or expectations of
others this will make you unhappy Pay attention
to yourself and only to yourself connect with your heart
feel focus on the feelings
and only then will you know exactly what you
want from you and for  you once you have
identified what you want be intense
immerse yourself in the sensation that you already have what
you desire feel that you already are what
you want to become
imagine and feel what it is like to have what you
desire feel what it is like to be that
person you want to be imagine yourself having
and being
imagine yourself living with that happy and
joyful print positive emotions and
details like color or smell
remember to always be intense very intense
in the sensations and
emotions if you are lukewarm the universe will
throw overboard what you say you
want you cannot do anything or
manifest anything if you are lukewarm you must be
intense about it want to be rich it is
okay to be rich want to be known it does
not matter but it must be intense in this
moment that you are flooded with emotions
and sensations being and having what you
want to be and have repeat the phrase
I am and mention what you want I am
abundance I am healthy I have
a paid job and I earn more than I have
ever earned do not affirm in the future
Affirm in the present if you affirm in the
future you give the instruction to your
brain that you lack in the present what you
desire it is a state of
lack Do not ask God for anything implying
a state of lack because God is a
mirror and will give you more lack since
this is the state in which you are
asking since God is in you
speak to your heart and feel the reward of
what you are asking from a state
of
abundance maintain that state and go to sleep
just sleep without wondering how why
or through whom you will get what you
want Do not let the mind talk about
how you get it and why the
conscience is empty without the voice of the
mind without your Earthly character thinking
the how why is not your job nor does it
concern your conscious mind rational the
next day Get up and do all
the actions that go according to the
achievement of your goal or objective but
from a state of abundance knowing
that you already are or have what you desire
if you yearn if you attach yourself to the goal it is a
state of lack where you know that you do not
have or are in the present what you
want the universe will give you more of that
lack and your work from the
previous night will be hindered or even
discarded be certain that what you
want is already part  of you and your
reality and that although there is work or
actions to do to
physically manifest it, those actions are the way you
show the universe that you
truly are what you say you
want with your feeling of doing and
obtaining what you want and with your
actions the Universe will realize that you
truly are what you
say you want and it will have no choice but to
bring you closer to that which is similar to you, that is to
say, it will make things easier for you. It will
bring you new answers, new ideas,
new ways to
physically manifest what you want. Do not
ask yourself how it can be possible,
simply feel that you already have it. It
is not your mind's job to solve the
How or the Why or to look for new
paths, that is the job of the universe.
Once your feelings, your
thoughts, and your actions are
constantly aligned, I will repeat
this and I hope you learn it to
apply it in your life, thoughts,
feelings, and actions
constantly aligned. The work of the mind is to
eloquently carry out the
actions of day to day life that are
aligned with your feelings and
thoughts. The universe will provide you with
the answers to the How. They will come
suddenly, just like that, without wanting to
obtain them, they will come in the form of
sudden ideas, revelations, inspiration,
willing people.  apparent qualities
dreams things or inexplicable situations
the outside will begin to move in your
favor most of the time without you
realizing it It is important to know that even if you do not
realize it behind the curtain
the gears of the universe will be working in
your favor your job is not to solve or
search with your mind that task you will have already
done before sleeping and the
Universe is taking care of that your
day to day work is to carry out the
actions that are in accordance with
your objective and along the way identify
what comes as divine help, that is to
say, identify the new
favorable circumstances or the
sudden ideas or the people who come
as if by chance and flow with them
with more
actions this has to be very clear
for this to work your job is to
identify not to search since searching
implies the state of lack and what
you have to do is confirm to the
universe that you are and you have that which you say you
want so during your
actions you must feel the state of
abundance and carry out your plans and
actions without searching
allowing them to come to you alone and in
a way that nobody knows Neither you nor your
superficial mind everything will come to pass
everything in this world was created this
way but  Man does not know he is not
aware of his own wonderful
essence of I am his consciousness
his wonderful human imagination that is
God all that you behold in this
world this universe although it may appear
external is within your imagination and
this world of mortality is but
a shadow of that imagination and of that
which is within you you are light
illuminating the object of your desire which
casts a shadow in the world the
physical manifestation of that
object so you can change the shadow
in the world if you change the object because
you are the light change the object that you
carry within you and identify with
it and you who are sufficient light
will cast a new shadow upon the
world there are people who earn
a ton of money yet they are
incapable of passing any
college entrance exams they
can't even keep their accounts or use the
products that they sell they are earning
millions because that was their goal in
life they have the intention of doing it and they
know they are capable and they are holders of that
inner abundance nevil godar tells us
that if we want fame or money as a
goal that's fine however his
deepest desire his dream his goal is that
Our goal is to awaken to who we
really are When the  Man
awakens from this dream the whole vast
world and all it contains is nothing
to the being that is the subconscious mind it is
like a garden in the earth but with
infinite power what you plant by
repeated thoughts and feelings
followed by actions will grow in the
outside world with such an
experience what a relief to know that everything I
experience is the result of my
own standard of belief that I am the
center of my own web of
circumstances and as I change so
must my outside world change
the law of assumption the law of
assumption tells you that all of creation is already
finished all the good that you
could ever want or need in life has already been
created for you
then you don't even have to create
anything but manifest that which has already been
created in the field of all
possibilities health wealth success
your heart's desires
etc manifesting is your
innate ability with the law of assumption you
understand that you no longer attract things but you
manifest those things then the
world that you perceive is not an entity
outside of you or alien to you but a reflection
of yourself neville said the world
is yourself expelled which
agrees perfectly with  the philosophy
of Ho'oponopono and the creation of
reality through parallel universes
But we will talk about that another time
the law of Assumption explains that you
are the center of your universe you are the
creator the manifestor and the God of your
world which puts you in a
more advantageous position when it comes to manifesting
than the simple act of attracting things
while the law of attraction
speaks of that you must stay aligned
with your desire and think a lot about it and
then release it the law of Assumption says
that you must become your desire
then that desire is already in your
physical world it says that everything in your
world is a reflection of you so if you
want to manifest something you must conceive it
in your mind as something already finished and
become your desire then here there is
no longer a need to
consciously raise your vibration or stay in
tune with the object of your desire the
only thing you need to do is assume and
feel your desire as if you already had it
absolutely all of us apply the law of
Assumption in our lives in one way or
another for better or for worse well we
all have  assumptions about
ourselves about life about money
etcetera and those assumptions manifest
in our life experience your life has been
created by all of the assumptions
that you've had over time and
those assumptions activate the law of
assumption everything that you take for granted in the
world what you take for granted about
others and what you take for granted about
yourself is reflected in your life you are the
projector of your own life on the
screen of space and if you don't like what you
see in your experience what you must
do is change in yourself and within yourself
the images that you are
projecting this is why most
people have such a hard time
manifesting with the law of attraction
people feel isolated from the
things they want to manifest they don't
integrate them into their being and only try to
attract them which doesn't always work I
repeat in the law of
assumption there is nothing to attract you only
have to conceive it in your mind and
experience the sensation of the desire already
fulfilled in the law of assumption you create
and manifest you do not attract that is why nevil
said that what you believe and  you assume that it is
true it becomes your reality so
for you to understand better what we
are talking about you are the God of your
world and you create your external world
through your internal world the money you
earn your relationships the type of job you
have your health status
absolutely everything in your life
is a projection of yourself it is a reflection of
the images and assumptions within you your
inner world projects all of those things
into your life in fact the true and only
reality in your inner world is what you
see and experience it is only the reflection of
that inner reality within you in other words an
illusion a matrix created or projected
by you so based on the above
to manifest a desire or
anything you want or transform your entire
life for the better you must create an
inner state in which your desire is already
fulfilled you must embody the state of your
desire already realized if your desire has already been fulfilled it has already been
realized then
what are the feelings that you are
experiencing right now at the moment when you
manage to create the reality of your
desire in your inner world at that very
moment your desire is already yours it already
belongs to you then you must create an
inner state where you already have that which
You desire so much but as long as your state does not
match your desire you will not be able to
manifest it because we do not
manifest what we want, we manifest what we are and
if we manifest what we are. Then you
cannot manifest wealth if you feel
poor, nor can you manifest a
good relationship if you feel lonely or
manifest a job if you feel
unemployed. It is understood that we do not manifest what
we want consciously but what
we are in our inner state, what we
are
projecting. Well, I repeat here we are not
trying to attract anything but we
give ourselves the task of changing the
mental images that are being projected in
our life in the same way that a
projector and a movie screen the
projector is us and our
imaginative capacity and the screen is
the Canvas of our life. If we do not
like what we are seeing reflected in
the Canvas of our life, we do not go to the
Canvas and try to change it, but
we change the
images that we must project in the projector. With the
law of Assumption you can have and
experience everything you desire, the
only limits are imposed by your
imagination. Many people who study
the law of attraction fail to
manifest anything until they know the law
of Assumption.  and this makes a lot of
sense because with the law of Assumption
you know that any desire you may have
already belongs to you it has already been created
for you and you only have to claim it in the
law of Assumption we do not ask or
beg we claim what is already
ours let's give a
practical example so you understand how to do
this let's suppose you want to manifest
a certain amount of money that you
need what you should do is not
only think about that money that you desire
but create it in your imagination and
feel it in your hands not as something that is
going to manifest one day but as
something that is already as real here and now
as your own hands and that is already there
for you then you are going to evoke in yourself the
sensation of the desire already fulfilled without a
doubt that money is already in your
possession feel it in your hands and
imagine yourself doing with it the things for which you
want it evokes in you
feelings of joy emotion and
gratitude play with those images
make them yours you can see how some
loved one congratulates you for having obtained
the money that you
needed so much you are going to do this as many
times as you want during the day at
night fall asleep with  the feeling of the
wish already fulfilled and think about what you are going to
do with that money count the money
in your imagination over and over again with
excitement until you fall asleep if you
do this you will be applying the law of
assumption and your money will have to
manifest so in summary ASSUME
the feeling of your wish already fulfilled and
refuse to give power to the apparent
evidences of your physical senses you now
know that these apparent
physical evidences are nothing more than reflections of your
past thinking maintain
this new inner state as long as possible
and your manifestation will be assured
throughout the day play with those
mental images the things you wish to see in your
life delight in your
directed imaginations it is not wasted time they are not
idle daydreams but the very
manifesting power of the universe operating in you
through
you now you know that your imagination creates
your reality you now understand that the
world you experience is not as physical
as it seems but is only the reflection
of your habitual imagination and your
everyday assumptions it is the reflection of who you
are apply the law of assumption
and transform your life you are the center of
your world and only  you can decide what to
see live and experience in it your
imagination is creative your imagination
is the software of the projector that you are
and the life you perceive is the screen
where the images are
projected your inner world is the only
reality that exists the world you
perceive outside are nothing more than reflections
of that internal reality of you I
sincerely wish that for your own good you
understand these truths that you yourself
can verify in your life and thus you can
fill your world with this abundance of
all good and true
prosperity if you only set the intention again
and again every night every
night before sleeping you accompany it with
actions and give it time you will be able to make
great manifestations in your life before we
say goodbye I want to give you these
powerful words so that you can
reflect listen to the superior man does
not see things as they are but as they should be